{
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "React",
      "description": "React Review",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "name": "Example ",
      "description": "this is an example\n",
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "name": "Empty",
      "description": "Empty Deck Example",
      "id": 6
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "ba",
      "back": "fr",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "b",
      "back": "b",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "front": "a",
      "back": "a",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "front": "b",
      "back": "a",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "b",
      "back": "a",
      "id": 9,
      "deckId": "4"
    },
    {
      "front": "a",
      "back": "a",
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "a",
      "back": "a",
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "a",
      "back": "a",
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": "b",
      "back": "a",
      "id": 13,
      "deckId": "4"
    },
    {
      "front": "State vs Variable",
      "back": "State rerenders component",
      "id": 14,
      "deckId": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "a",
      "back": "aasa",
      "id": 15,
      "deckId": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "a",
      "back": "a",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "front": "s",
      "back": "s",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 17
    },
    {
      "front": "s",
      "back": "s",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 18
    },
    {
      "front": "useHistory",
      "back": "History.push to go to a different page",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 19
    },
    {
      "front": "Switch",
      "back": "loads only 1 route",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 20
    },
    {
      "front": "useEffect()",
      "back": "runs after it renders",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 21
    },
    {
      "front": "Dependeny arrray",
      "back": "controls when useEffect runs",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 22
    }
  ]
}